Hello everyone, in today's video we are going to talk
about ICICI Prudential IPO.  So the allotments of this IPO have been done
and who all have been
allotted, please do let us know by commenting.
But for those who have not been allotted,
we will try to find out by when their money will be unlocked or refunded.  But the
best thing to be happy about is that
after allotment its GMP has rocketed again.
Updates are running around ₹2200.
But we are going to try to find out what percentage premium is there on one lot size.
But friends, we will
also see what good news is coming out before the listing
and there is a big expert who has
given updates of around 39% on this IPO.  That too after listing
but we will also
know how it has been given.  Also, friends, for those who have got
allotment in this IPO, we are going to try to
know what should be their future strategy.
So you must
stay till the end of the video.  Today's video is going to be
very important for all the allotment holders.
So friends, the allotment of the
IPO which ran from 12th December to 16th December has been
completed.
But you would have been given six equity shares at the price of ₹165
during allotment.  That too
within one lot size and this IPO which
was launched came through offer for sale
and as you can see the promoters
of the company will sell shares worth a total of ₹1602 crores
which you can see is around 48 89 sorry
4.90 crores.  So friends, all these have been
allotted here yesterday.
Late last night around 10:00 pm.
But friends, if you look further,
all these shares will be
completely listed on the BSE and NSE exchanges.
But friends, according to the timeline, today is a
very important day.  As
you will see, there is allotment here
which you must have come to know about late last night
but those who have not been allotted, their
money will be refunded today on 18th December and
those who have been allotted today, their
shares will be given in their demat account and you
can see those shares tomorrow
on Friday, 19th December, which are going to be completely
listed on BSE and NSC exchanges.
But friends, the refunding
process will proceed like this today.
But before that, friends, let me tell you
that if you have received a
debit message of ₹12,990 late last night, then you should understand that
friends, you have got the allotment and today
you have shares which will also be credited to your demat account.  Friends,
if you have got two
lot sizes then double multiply the two lots here.
You must have received a message of debit of around ₹25,000
and two lot sizes.
But friends, today
if you get an update of refunding here,
which is unlock revoke or
friends, you get credit messages from the
bank today, that too for ₹1990,
then you should understand that friends, today it is your
money which has been completely refunded
and you have not received the allotment.
But friends, if you see, the
total issue charge here was Rs 10602 crore.
But the company has received an amount of
₹96927
crore in return.  So friends, out of these, the company will
keep only ₹1600 crores with itself
and the company will refund the remaining amount.
So friends, now you should
understand that when such a huge amount of funds has been collected here within three days, then
you should understand that friends, it may take two to
three days time bill
in the process of your refund.  So friends, now
here, like today,
messages of unlock have started coming here.
Those who have not been allotted here.
So many messages have come from many people.
But friends, today around 80% of
everyone's money will be refunded here.
But the remaining 20% ​​will be refunded to
you tomorrow around 12:00 noon and the
refund process will be completed here.
So this is how friends are going to live here.
But now comes the biggest thing,
what is the good news before the closing.
First of all, friends, you can see
here the business of the company, the
information given through the offer note, the company manages
active mutual fund assets worth Rs 10.1 lakh crore
here.  So
friends, it means that it manages the mutual funds which have
₹1 lakh crore invested here.
It has a market share of 10.3% and
dominance in the equity and hybrid categories, with both revenue and profit growing at a 3-
year CGR of over 32%.
So friends, if we
look at these figures then only
friends the company has been able to become a better company here
and at the same time friends the
company has been
oversubscribed to the same extent.  But apart from that, if you
see, there are many such updates of the company
which you friends can also read.
Like here in the AAUME Equity Elimination
Plan the company is working on here.
Generally, there are better margins and
advisory services like PMF PMS and AIF, hence the
company is growing rapidly in them.
Friends, this gives a very good
positive update to the company here.
So friends, after looking at these figures, there is
a big expert, you can see
here, from PL Capital, and he
says that the ICI share here will definitely be
listed on Friday,
but this brokerage firm has
given buy updates, you can see it, and the IPO gets an
update of around 39% from the price here, but friends, you
can see this update here, in
which you can see that
ICICI Pashul AMC of PL Capital has given a
buy update on the shares that are going to be listed soon,
and has also fixed updates here around ₹3000.
But this means that the
company had fixed the issue price of ₹2165 here, so there
can be updates of around 39% from this price.  However, friends, the GMP that is
running here is around 20 17 20%.
Which we will definitely
see here.  But friends, you
can see further here that these brokerage fund houses
also say that
this optimism about the business prospects is due to its strong
performance and the parent company is driving this growth due to
highest net equity flow, market share among AMCs,
better equity yield and other reasons.
Meaning that friends, there is a company
which is expanding its business here.
Due to which friends, the
positive trend of the company here
is a big positive update.  Friends, you can see that
PL Capital has further said that
here, along with better distribution and diversification,
profitability and whatever updates are there here,
friends are turning towards this company.
So you can see that PL
Capital has given a great update on this company even
before the closing.
But now friends, let's talk about GMP in this company.
However,
friends, who have not yet found out
how to check the allotment status, then
this is the
official website of Caffeine Technology Limited company,
whose direct link we have made available
on our Telegram channel here late last night.
As soon as you click on it,
this interface will open and in
it, first of all, friends, you have to
select the name of the company, which is
appearing at the top here, and
after selecting it, fill in the application number, demat account or
PAN card, whatever details you have,
and submit it.  You will get
confirmation whether it has been allotted to you or
not.  But now
friends let's talk about its jumping GMP.  So
friends, if we talk about yesterday, then
you can almost see that here
its GMP has increased by around ₹24
and today's friends are still left here
because friends, today is the 18th and
here on the day of allotment, at
around 8:00 am in the morning, the
GMP of around ₹370 is running at ₹2165.  So if you
place a price of ₹370 instead of opening at ₹2165, then you
can see around ₹2535. The estimated
listing is giving updates which have displayed a premium of around 17%
and if we
talk about one lot size, then estimated updates of ₹2220 are
going on.  Meaning that
friends, as I have also written on the thumbnail, there is a
rise of around ₹2200 in GMP, so
friends, updates are going on here on the entire lot size i.e. six shares
at ₹2220.
But if we talk about the stock here, the
GMP is running at ₹370.  So friends, you
can see here that the company is doing much better
here, GMP is
being recorded here.  But friends, today let us
see what updates are there here and
whether there are statements from brokerage fund houses here, then
this GMP will be based on them
and in this, friends, Omo, an expert
here, as I have just shown, is
giving updates of 39% instead of 17%.  So 39% you can understand
how much it can be.  Please do let us
know by commenting once.  But friends, now whatever updates will be there
regarding this IPO, they will be provided to you in the next to
next video.
So you must subscribe to our channel.